thegnomonworkshop.com 2019-05-08

# Privacy Policies | The Gnomon Workshop

## PRIVACY POLICY

Gnomon’s privacy policy covers the collection and use of personal information that may be collected by Gnomon anytime you interact with Gnomon, such as when you visit our website, when you purchase Gnomon products, or when you call our sales or support associates. Please take a moment to read the following to learn more about our information practices, including what type of information is gathered, how the information is used and for what purposes, to whom we disclose the information, and how we safeguard your personal information. Your privacy is a priority at Gnomon, and we go to great lengths to protect it.

### Why we collect personal information

Because it helps us deliver a superior level of customer service.

### What information do we collect

There are a number of situations in which your personal information may help us give you better service. At such times, we may collect personal information relevant to the situation, such as your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, and contact preferences; your credit card information and information about the Gnomon products you own, such as their serial numbers, and date of purchase. We may collect information for market research purposes — such as your occupation and where you use your computer — to gain a better understanding of our customers and thus provide more valuable service. We may also collect information regarding customer activities on our website. This helps us to determine how best to provide useful information to customers and to understand which parts of our websites and Internet services are of most interest to them.

### When we disclose your information

Gnomon takes your privacy very seriously. Be assured that Gnomon does not sell or rent your contact information to other marketers. There are times when it may be advantageous for Gnomon to make certain personal information about you available to companies that Gnomon has a strategic relationship with or that perform work for Gnomon to provide products and services to you on our behalf. These companies may help us process information, extend credit, fulfill customer orders, deliver products to you, manage and enhance customer data, provide customer service, assess your interest in our products, or conduct customer research or satisfaction surveys. Without such information being made available, it would be difficult for you to purchase products, have products delivered to you, receive customer service, provide us feedback to improve our products and services, or access certain services, offers, and content on the Gnomon website.

At times we may be required by law or litigation to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary.

### Protecting your personal information

You can help us by also taking precautions to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often using a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure web browser like Safari.

### Integrity of your personal information

Gnomon has safeguards in place to keep your personal information accurate, complete, and up to date for the purposes for which it is used. Naturally, you always have the right to access and correct the personal information you have provided.

Gnomon may update its privacy policy from time to time. When we change the policy in a material way a notice will be posted on our website along with the updated privacy policy.

The information contained in this web site is subject to change without notice.

Copyright © The Gnomon Workshop, Inc. All rights reserved.  
The Gnomon Workshop, Inc., 1015 North Cahuenga Boulevard, Hollywood, CA 90038.
